dynalist.io 2018-11-01

# Privacy Policy - Dynalist

Dynalist values the privacy of our users and makes all reasonable efforts to protect it. This Privacy Policy covers the collection, use and disclosure of personal information that may be collected when you use Dynalist, such as when you use our services or communicate with the Dynalist Support team. Please read the following to learn more about what information we collect, what we do with that information, and how we may use your personal information.

We value your privacy and below is how we protect it.

### Information Collection and Use

We collect certain personal information because we want to provide the best possible service. It enables us to deliver product announcements, service updates and special offers as well as provide convenient and personalized user access and improve the features and usability of our products. Unregistered users may still be able to use certain Dynalist services, in which case no personal information is collected.

We collect information for internal business purposes in a number of situations, including but not limited to: personal information such as name and e-mail address; geographic information such as where you use your devices to improve our understanding of our customer needs; tracking information about your visit, including IP address, cookies and the pages you request to analyze trends and administer the site; aggregate information from multiple users without personally identifying individuals, which we may share with our partners to improve understanding of customer needs and provide relevant services. 

We collect your email address to send stuff we think you'd care about. We collect some other stuff for internal use only.

### Public Information

Certain parts of the Dynalist website and services are open to any online viewer, such as documents designated as "public." Any information that you post in these locations can be read, collected and used by anyone, and could enable others to send you unsolicited messages. Our service enables you to determine whether or not to post personal or otherwise sensitive information to publically accessible areas of our site, and so you should carefully consider how you use the services. Dynalist is not responsible for any publication or use of any personal information you choose to post in these locations.

If you decide to share your document publicly, it's open for anyone to see. Please think twice before doing so.

### Information Disclosure to Third Parties

We do not share, sell, rent or otherwise distribute information you enter in Dynalist to others, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. We may share your information with others outside of Dynalist under the following circumstances:

  * We have your explicit consent to share the information;
  * We need to share your information to fulfill your product or service request, such as backing up your data in a third party file storage service like Dropbox;
  * We have a good faith belief that sharing or otherwise permitting access, disclosure, use or preservation of such information is reasonably necessary in order to comply with our legal obligations;
  * We believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or potential threats against persons or property.

We may share your information with third parties when you agree to it or when we're required by law to do so.

### Use of Cookies

Cookies are small data files that a website you visit may save on your device that usually includes an anonymous unique identifier. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses, or capture your personal information. Our service uses cookies for user authentication, keeping track of your preferences, promotional campaigns that require user identification, keeping track of our audience size and traffic patterns, and in certain other cases.

Depending on which browser you use, you can normally configure your browser to accept cookies, reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being used. However, if you configure your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use our service that require you to sign in or take full advantage of our features.

We may allow third party business partners that display advertisements on some of our web pages to maintain their own cookies on your computer. These business partners do not have access to our cookies and their use is subject to their own privacy policies.

We use cookies so that we can identify you. Cookies won't do harm in most cases, but you can disable it, in which case you probably won't be able to use Dynalist :(

### Links

Our website and service may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policy or other practices employed by websites linked to, or from, our website nor the information or content contained therein. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by us.

Be careful when clicking third party links.

### Data Ownership

You own the data you put into Dynalist. By putting your information into Dynalist, you do not grant us any special rights with regard to that information.

You own your data. Period.

### Data Security

We're committed to protect your information. We do the following to make sure your information is secure:

  * Your password is protected by encryption and only you have access to it;
  * Your personal information and data stored in our systems is protected by various physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. Our employees do not monitor or view your personal information or content stored in our service, but it may be viewed if we learn that our Terms of Service may have been violated and confirmation is required, or we otherwise determine that we have an obligation to review it;
  * Our service uses standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions. SSL encryption is a technology used by thousands of leading online services such as banks, email providers and remote backup services. However, this is not a guarantee that such data transmissions cannot be accessed, altered or deleted due to firewall or other security software failures.

If we learn of a security system breach we may attempt to notify you and provide information on protective steps, if available, through the e-mail address that you supplied during registration or posting a notice on our website.

We do our best to protect your data. Your password is encrypted, and all data transmission is protected by SSL encryption. Having said that, we can't guarantee 100% security.

### International Users

Personal information collected by us may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Dynalist maintains facilities, and by using this website, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

Your data will be stored and processed in the country we host our servers, no matter which country you live in.

### Changes and Updates

As this Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time, we will revise and display the effective date at the top of the web page. You should periodically review it to keep abreast of our plans and procedures to protect the personal information that we collect. Your continued use of our services constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

If Dynalist should ever sell its assets, merge with another entity or file for bankruptcy, information collected from this web site and in the operation of the services may be transferred as assets of Dynalist.

We may change these policies when necessary. We'll tell you in advance when it affects you.

Your information may be transferred as assets of Dynalist if we're bought by another company.

By " **transferred as assets** ", we mean the buyer company will store your data so that it can provide the service. You will still own your data.
